# Bhaumikbhai Sanjaykumar Trivedi Bachelor of Engineering (Civil Engineering) Mo: 9723091432

E-mail: bhaumik.trivedi.90@gmail.com

## **Career Objective:**

Dedicated professional with more than 5 years of proven track record in the field of client services, project management and operations. Currently looking for suitable and challenging opportunities that can enhance my professional development with client services, account management and operations roles.

# **Academic Background:**

Course	School	Academic year
B.E. Civil Engineering	Sigma Institute of Engineering,	2014-2018
	Gujarat Technical University,(GTU Board)	
HSC	Jay Jalaram International School, (Gujarat board)	2014
SSC	Jay Jalaram International School, (Gujarat board)	2012

# **Work Experience:**

**Last Organization:** MAGNIT Global **Position:** Supplier Validation Analyst

**Duration:** September, 2021 to October, 2023

#### Responsibilities:

- Magnit Global is a MSP (managed service provider) that connects the clients to the suppliers. As a Supplier Validation Analyst, I was responsible for handling the client programs and supplier onboarding process.
- One of my main roles includes the client project implementation where I worked as an Implementation Specialist for US and EU based clients. Serving as the primary liaison between the suppliers and clients.
- Interacting regularly with client team to keep them updated about on-going program status and to discuss supplier queries. .
- I was also taking care of creating and managing client program spreadsheets for supplier set ups, worker enrollments as well as coordinating and collecting required data elements from the suppliers or workers around on-boarding.
- Managing client account in VMS and keeping a track of documents and on-boarding process.
- Working closely with the program managers for meeting task deliverables and deadlines. I was also responsible for implementation of client specific requirements

including supplier setups, coordinating with clients, suppliers and internally with the different teams to ensure all aspects of the setup process are taken care of from front to back.

- Distributing communications, training materials, invites, videos, FAQs, supplier handbooks to assist in hitting project plan milestones.
- Maintain productivity and efficiency while supporting implementations in multiple time zones
- Developing and maintaining professional and productive ongoing client relationships by maintaining regular contact and building strong rapport with key decision makers within the client organization like VP, directors, key finance team members, account managers, legal team members.

**Organization**: Numerator **Position**: Data Associate

Duration: March, 2021 to September, 2021

# Responsibilities:

• I was responsible for doing ads and market research and provide valuable insights to the client teams based on which they can get better idea of consumer's behavior and plan their marketing strategy.

Organization: Panchal Consultant and Services

**Position:** Consultant & Engineer

Duration: October, 2019 to November, 2020

### Responsibilities:

- Panchal Consultant and Services is a Project Management Consultancy. As a part of PMC, I was responsible for managing clients and handling their projects.
- Doing Meetings with clients to keep them updated about on-going progress, building and maintaining a strong professional relationship.
- Coordinating with various teams and entities involved to ensure smooth work flow.
- Supervising the work to make sure everything is compliant as per IS codes and client needs.
- Preparing project management plans, task schedules, reports, presentations and providing technical guidance.

Organization: Freelancing
Positions: Client' Web Manager
Duration: May, 2018 to August, 2019

# Responsibilities:

- Handling client' web publishing program, taking care of keyword research and search engine optimization (SEO).
- Interacting and meeting clients to understand their niche, expectations and requirements.
- Preparing monthly progress report, analyzing the publishing strategy and data.

#### **Academic Projecte**

Rubber Concrete - Designed the M25 grade concrete then replaced the coarse aggregate by different percentages of scrap rubber aggregate in concrete and carried out workability and compressive strength tests to find out the optimum percentage by which the scrap rubber aggregate can be utilized in the concrete.

# **Publications**

- Published a research paper on "Study Of A Rubber As A Construction Material" in the international journal IJSRSET (International Journal of Scientific Research in Science, Engineering and Technology).
- Online ISSN: 2394-4099, Print ISSN: 2395-1990, Volume 4 Issue 5, page no.94-98, March-April 2018.

## **Technical Skills Set:**

- Client Management
- Microsoft 365
- Google Workspace
- Power BI
- SQL
- Data Analysis
- Vendor Management System (VMS)
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Content Writing
- Project Management
- Account Management
- AutoCAD

#### **Hobbies:**

- Writing and reading poetry
- Playing cricket and chess
- Watching movies and Formula 1 racing

# **Extra-Curricular:**

- Core member in technical fest held in my college in the years 2017 and 2018.
- Teaching basics of poetry to new writers.
- Co-Ordinator for college fest for three years.
- Participated in 2nd international conference on current research trends in engineering and technology organized under SIEICON 2018.

## **Declaration:**

I hereby, declare that the information furnished here is correct to the best of my knowledge. Thanking you and awaiting your favorable reply.